<NumDialogues>10</NumDialogues>
<DialogueOne>
  <Text>The year is 65,000,000 B.C. and life is pretty okay -
    or as okay as it gets as the son of a travelling VelociReporter.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueOne>
<DialogueTwo>
  <Text>Your name is Phillip Osoraptor, and you've finally moved back to your
    home valley, reuniting with one of your only childhood friends, Diana Tyrana.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueTwo>
<DialogueThree>
  <Text>Diana seems to remember you fondly, but you find yourself nervous and
    stuttering whenever your herds meet at the watering hole. Each day you
    tell yourself it'll work out better tomorrow.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueThree>
<DialogueFour>
  <Text>With hopes of reconnecting with Diana in your heart and maybe finally
    settling down, life in your new valley seems hopeful and promising.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueFour>
<DialogueFive>
  <Text>... Well, until the whole "meteor" thing happens at least.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueFive>
<DialogueSix>
  <Text>It's been a few months since then, and your once lush and beautiful valley
    is now barren and dry. There are no more Raptor Races or games of Brontosaurus
    Ball; most herds are migrating out of the valley in a desperate hope for survival.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueSix>
<DialogueSeven>
  <Text>But way more importantly, everyone's trying to get with your girl.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueSeven>
<DialogueEight>
  <Text>With many of the female dinosaurs gone, everyone's attention has turned to 
    Diana to try to continue their species survival.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueEight>
<DialogueNine>
  <Text>If only there were some way to finally show her that you cared about her
    first...</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueNine>
<DialogueTen>
  <Text>Hey, Phil! It's good to see a friendly face around... It's been kind of lonely
    since the meteor, what with everyone leaving, huh?</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueTen>
<DialogueEleven>
  <Text>The valley still feels too much like home to me to leave just yet. I guess
    I mostly just miss how green everything was. I mean, I'm no herbivore, but that
    doesn't mean I couldn't still appreciate all the flower fields, you know?</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueEleven>
<DialogueTwelve>
  <Text>Just wishful thinking, I guess. Anyway, I better get back to my herd...
  It was nice talking to you, Phil.</Text>
  <Background></Background>
</DialogueTwelve>
